Guide to the Park Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- APPENDIX A: INDEX TO SELECTED CORRESPONDENCE
  - Lincoln, Abraham, pres. U.S. (1809-1865). ALS to Norman Buel Judd. Springfield, Ill., August 3, 1860 (Box 7)
  - Lindsley, Philip (1786-1855). Testimonial in favor of the Question Books on the Assembly's Shorter Catechism, by the Rev. A. R. New Albany, Ind., March 23, 1853 (Box 7)
  - Livingston, John Henry (1746-1825). ALS to Gen. Van Rensselaer. New Brunswick, N.J., June 23, 1819
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.41
  - Livingston, Robert (1746-1813). ALS to Steven Lusk. Clermont, [N.Y.], Nov, 26, 1795
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.8
  - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (1807-1882). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Cambridge, Mass., February 17, 1838
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.49
  - Longfellow, Stephen (1776-1849). ALS to Edward Cutts. Portland [Me.], November 24, 1829
  - Lotze, Rudolf Hermann (1817-1881). ALS in German to Edwards A. Park. Göttingen, Germany, October 16, 1880 (Box 7)
  - Lovejoy, Owen (1811-1864). ALS to the Rev. Edwards A. Park. Washington, December 17, 1862
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.59
  - Lover, Samuel (ALS to Messrs. Firth & Hall. [New York], December 11, 1846
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.28
  - Lyon, Mary (1797-1849).
    - 2 ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. South Hadley, Mass., January 16, 1840; [no month] 27, 1841 (Box 7)
    - ALS to Jerusha Williams (Billings) Edwards. South Hadley, Mass., July 16, 1841 (Box 7)
  - Lytton, Edward George Earle Lytton Bulwer-Lytton, 1st Baron, (1803-1873). ALS to A. Blackwood. [n.p.], June 12, 1843
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.25
  - Macaulay, Thomas Babington Macaulay, 1st baron (1800-1859).
    - Note in the third person to Mr. and Mrs. John Shaw-Lefevre. Albany, May 20, 1837
    - ALS to Thomas Spring-Rice. London, [ca. 1834]? (Box 6)
  - Macaulay, Zachary (1768-1838).
    - Letter to the Rev. W. Hopkins. Freetown, Sierra Leone, March 19, 1795
    - Copy of letter to Jedidiah Morse. London, July 20, 1815 (Box 4)
  - McAuley, Thomas (1768-1852). ALS to Benjamin B. Wisner. Philadelphia, January 19, 1832 (Box 6)
  - McClure, David (1748-1820). ALS to the Rev. Dr. Wheelock. Fort Pitt, Pa., February 16, 1773
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.11
  - McCosh, James (1811-1894). 2 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Philadelphia and Houston, July 4, 1866; July 71, 1866 (Box 7)
  - McCrie, Thomas (1772-1835). Letter in the third person to James Haig. Newington [Scot.], September 17, 1825
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.40
  - MacDonald, George (1824-1905). ALS to Mr. Allon [Henry Allon (1818-1892)]? London, [undated] (Box 8)
  - MacFarlan, Duncan. ALS to Benjamin B. Wisner. Renfrew Morse, Scot., August 16, 1831 (Box 6)
  - MacGregor, Sir James. ALS to Sir [unnamed person]. Notingham [sic], March 20, 1841
  - McIlvaine, Joshua (1815-1897). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Newark, N.J., May 13, 1876 (Box 7)
  - McKinley, William, pres. U.S. (1843-1901). Autograph.
    See: box 10, folder 123
  - McLane, Louis (1786-1857). ALS to Asbury Dickins. Wilmington, Del., November 3, 1828
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.42
  - McLean, John (1785-1861). ALS to R. Smith. [Washington], January 8, 1834
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.46
  - Madison, Dolly (Payne) Todd (1768-1849). Autograph social note in the third person to the President [Martin Van Buren]. Washington, January 19, 1839
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.38
  - Madison, James, pres. U.S. (1750/51-1836). ALS to Thomas Jefferson. Montpellier [Va.], March 16, 1819
  - Malan, Henri Abraham César (1787-1864). ALS to Messrs. Sidney E. Morse & Co. Geneva, Switzerland, [undated]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.6
  - Mantell, Gideon Algernon (1790-1852). 2 ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. London, [June 4, 1846; Junee 9, 1846] (Box 7)
  - Marheineke, Philipp Konrad (1780-1846). ALS in German to Fouqué. Berlin, Germany, December 31, 1814 (Box 4)
  - Marlborogh, George Spencer. 5th duke of, (1766-1840). ALS to Charles Tilt. Blenheim, England, July 20, 1834 (Box 6)
  - Marsh, James (1794-1842). ALS to the Board of Trustees of Phillips Academy. Andover, Mass., August 25, 1818 (Box 5)
  - Marshall, John (1755-1835). ALS to an unnamed person. Washington, March 12, 1818
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.22
  - Mason, John Mitchell (1770-1829). ALS to the Rev. Dr. Ashbel Green. New York, November 5, 1802
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.40
  - Massachusetts (Colony). Governor, 1679-1686 (Bradstreet). Warrant to the keeper of the prison in Boston for the imprisonment of John Dyer on the charge of killing an Indian. Boston, February 3, 1680
  - Massachusetts, Governor, 1780-1785 (John Hancock). Authorisation to Joseph Hawley and Ephraim Wright to take depositions in the case of Hannah Elwell praying divorce from Moses Elwell, signed by John Hancock and John Avery, Jr. Seal of the Commonwealth attached., July 6, 1734
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.6
  - Massachusetts Historical Society. Acknowledgement of gift recieved from Agnes Park; signed by C. F. Adams, president, and Samuel A. Green, librarian. Boston, October 30, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Massachusetts. Treasurer. Promissory note payable to the bearer in connection with a lottery; signed by H. Gardner, treasurer, and John Sollay and Edward Green, committemen. Boston, June 1, 1779 (Box 1)
  - Mather, Cotton (1662/63-1727/28). ALS to an unnamed person. [n.p.], [undated]
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.9
  - Mather, Increase (1639-1723). Notes on passages of scripture, not signed. [n.p.], [undated]
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.7
  - Mather, Richard (1596-1669). Fragment of a sermon, partly in shorthand, unsigned. [n.p.], [undated]
  - Matthews, Stanley (1824-1889). ALS to John C. Staples. Cincinatti, Ohio, April 12, 1879 (Box 7)
  - Mayhew, Elizabeth (Clark) (1734-). 2 AL and 1 ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Boston and Waltham, Mass.:
    - October 31, 1774 (Box 1)
    - September 17, 1780 (Box 1)
    - July 6, [n.y.] (Box 8)
  - Mellen, Prentiss (1764-1840). ALS to Charles Davis. Boston, January 27, 1810
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.22
  - Melvill, Henry (1798-1871). ALS to the Rev. Edwards A. Park. Hertford, March 20, 1844
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.41
  - Merriman, Daniel (1838-1812). ALS to Edwards A. Park. North Conway, N.H., July 12, 1873 (Box 7)
  - Messer, Asa (1769-1836). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Providence, R.I., October 18, 1809 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Thomas (1807-1874). ALS to David Bogue. Walworth, Eng., September 4, 1849 (Box 7)
  - Miner, Alonzo Ames (1814-1895). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Boston, January 10, 1878 (Box 7)
  - Mitchell, Donald Grant (1822-1908). AL (signed with initials) to Luther Tucker. New York, March 26, 1847
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.51
  - Mitford, Mary Russell (1787-1867). ALS to an unnamed person, Three Mile Cross, [ca. 1836] (Box 6)
  - Mittermaier, Karl Joseph Anton (1787-1867). Voucher in German that C. F. Sevin, a student, will return books borrowed from the Heidelberg Univ. Library. Printed form filled in. Heidelberg, Germany, February 1, 1840
  - Moffat, Robert (1795-1883). ALS to the Rev. F. Monod. Queen's Row, September 1841
  - Monroe, James, pres. U.S. (1758-1831). ALS to an unnamed person. Washington, June 5, 1816
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.40
  - Montgomery, James (1771-1854). ALS to an unnamed person. Fulneck near Leeds [Eng.], December 8, 1847
  - Morris, Robert (1734-1806). ALS to Thomas Morris. Philadelphia, January 5, 1801
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.2
  - Morrison, Robert (1782-1834). ALS to Capt. Moore, an American in China. [n.p.], October 3, 1817
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.43
  - Mueller, ____. Notes in Latin. [n.p.], [undated]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.10
  - Mueller, Julius (1801-1878). Letter in third person to Bela Bates Edwards. Halle, Germany, October 2 [1846] (Box 7)
  - Mulready, William (1786-1863). Receipt to Charles Tilt. London, March 12, 1833 (Box 6)
  - Murat, Achille. ALS in French to W. Bayard, Jr. Philadelphia, January 4, 1824
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.61
  - Murat, Prince Napoléon Lucien Charles, ALS in French to ____. Philadelphia, September 9, 1825
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.62
  - Murdock, James (1776-1856). ALS to Edward A. Pearson. Andover, Mass., January 17, 1853 (Box 7)
  - Murray, Alexander (1775-1813). Part of a glossary of terms transcribed into English chiefly from Anglo-Saxon. [n.p.], [undated]
  - Murray, John (1778-1843). ALS to Charles Tilt. London, Tuesday [n.y.] (Box 8)
  - Musgrave, Charles. ALS to Edwards A. Park. Halifax, Yorks., November 24, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Nairn, Miss E. K. ALS to Edwards A. Park. Glasgow, November 27, 1871 (Box 7)
  - Neal, John (1793-1876). ALS to Robert Carter. Portland, Me., August 8, 1842
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.35
  - Neander, Johann August Wilhelm (1789-1850).
    - ALS in German to Frédéric Monod. Berlin, Jul[?] 15, 1844
    - LS in German to Mr. Uhlenbull. [n.p.], [undated] (Box 8)
  - Necker, Jacques (1732-1804). ALS in French to ____. Coppet, Switzerland, July 29, 1803
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.47
  - Neff, Félix (1798-1829). ALS in French to ____. London, April 15, 1823
  - Nettleton, Asabel (1783-1844). 2 ALS to Francis L. Robbins. Baltimore and Philadelphia, January 10, 1834; March 28, 1834 (Box 6)
  - New York (State). Governor, 1818-1823 (Clinton). Appointment of Henry Edwards as ansign of a company in the Battalion of Riflemen in Greene Co., N.Y. Signed by DeWitt Clinton, Governor, and John Van Ness Yates, Sec. Printed form filled in. Albany, April 25, 1821 (Box 5)
  - New York (State) Militia. Discharge of Henry Edwards from military duty in the Regiment of Riflemen of the New York State Militia, signed by William W. Edwards, commanding officer. Hunter, Greene Co., N.Y., March 20, 1826 (Box 5)
  - Newman, John Henry, Cardinal (1801-1890). ALS probably to Edwards A. Park. The Oratory, London, February 27, 1879 (Box 7)
  - Niemcewicz, Juljan Ursyn (1757-1841). LS in French to William MacLure. Warsaw, Poland, June 28, 1830
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.64
  - Neimeyer, August Hermann (1754-1828?). ALS in German to ____. [n.p.], November 26, 1827
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.45
  - Nott, Eliphalet (1773-1866).
    - ALS to J. B. Brinsmade. Schenectady, N.Y., March 9, 1850
    - ALS to F. W. Olcot. Schenectady, N.Y., March 19, 1853
  - Ogden, Aaron (1756-1839). ALS to Ebenexer Elmor. Elizabeth Town [N.J.], March 16. 1787
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.16
  - Ogden, Robert (1716-1787). ALS to Rhoda (Ogden) Edwards. Elizabethtown, N.J., December 4, 1771 (Box 1)
  - Osgood, Samuel (1812-1880). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Fairfield, Conn., October 28, 1873 (Box 7)
  - Otis, James (1725-1783). Answer to the Probate court, Province of Massachusetts Bay as attorney for the nieces and nephews of James Allen, dec., to the complaint of Francis Wells, and other not named., [undated]
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.2
  - Owen, Rose T. (1771-1858). ALS to an unnamed person. (Probably to Joseph Lancester.) New Lanark [Scotland], [1811]
  - Palmer, George Herbert (1842-1933). ALS to Agnes Park. Cambridge, Mass., January 19, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Park, Agnes. ALS to Gail Hamilton [i.e. Mary Abigail Dodge]. Andover, Mass., June 1, 1865 (Box 7)
  - Park, Edwards Amasa (1808-1900).
    - "Can anyone be saved without a change of heart in this life?" An essay delivered before the Theological Society of Brown University. Providence, R.I., June 26, 1824 (Box 4)
    - Hotel Bill to Edwards Amasa Park. Hanover, Germany, September 22 - October 23, 1863 (Box 7)
  - Parker, Theodore (1810-1860). 2 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Boston:
    - February 17. 1847 (Box 7)
    - October 13, 1853
  - Parsons, David (1749-1823). ALS to Eleazar Wheelock. Amherst, Mass., July 29, 1771
  - Parsons, Jonathan (1705-1776). ALS to Eleazar Wheelock. Newburyport, Mass., June 28, 1774
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.29
  - Parsons, Sarah (Edwards) (1728-1805).
    - ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Stockbridge, Mass., March 20, 1770 (Box 1)
    - ALS to Lucy (Edwards) Woodbridge. Stockbridge, Mass., January 15, 1753/4 (Box 1)
  - Parsons, Theophilus (1750-1813). Certification as J.P. to the deposition of William Tallman in the case of the vessel Venus, claimed on behalf of the State of South Carolina. Essex, Mass., July 22, 1777
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.20
  - Paton, John Gibson (1824-1907). 2 ALS to William E. Park. Worcester and Boston, March 3, 1893; July 14, 1893 (Box 8)
  - Peabody, Oliver William Bourn (1799-1848). ALS to Charles Steward Daveis. Boston, September 1, 1833
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.36
  - Pearson, Eliphalet (1752-1826). Signed promise of his intention to repay his father the money expended for Eliphalet's education at college. [n.p.], October 30, 1769 (Box 1)
  - Peel, Sir Robert (1788-1850). Note in the third person to Mr. Kennedy. [London], August 2, 1830
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.18
  - Pemberton, Ebenezer (1671-1717). Certification to the marriage of Gilbert Colsworthy [i.e. Colesworthy] and Sarah Larkin. Boston, February 19, 1702
  - Pepperell, Sir William, 1st bart. (1696-1759). ALS to Messrs. Oliver & Welsteed. Kittery, Me., December 6, 1718 (Box 1)
  - Perabo, Johann Ernst (1845-1920).
    - ALS to an unnamed person, probably Agnes Park. Boston, July 25, 1897 (Box 8)
    - ALS to Miss Park. Boston, May 25, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Perthes, Friedrich Andreas. LS in German to Edwards A. Park(?). Gotha, Germany, September 20, 1865
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.22
  - Pestalozzi, Johann Heinrich (1746-1827). Receipt written in German for his salary as accessioner in the Royal Library at Hottingen (?).
  - Phelps, Austin (1820-1890). ALS to Samuel Farrar. Andover, Mass., February 17, [1858] (Box 7)
  - Philip, Robert (1791-1858).
    - 2 ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. London, June 6(?), 1846; June 8, 1846 (Box 7)
    - ALS to Ralph Wardlaw. London, June 8, 1846 (Box 7)
  - Phillips, Samuel (1752-1802).
    - Receipt to Eliphalet Pearson. Andover, Mass., April 13, 1785 (Box 1)
    - ALS to John Phillips. Andover, Mass., October 17, 1797 (Box 2)
  - Phillips, Wendell (1811-1884). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Boston, March 4, 1871 (Box 7)
  - Phillips, William (1750-1827). Letter in the third person to Benjamin B. Wisner. Boston, September 25, 1824 (Box 5)
  - Phillips Academy, Andover, Mass. Notification (draft) to John Adams (1772-1863) of his election as Principal of Phillips Academy, signed by Eliphalet Pearson, president, and M. Newman, clerk. Andover, Mass., August 24, 1809 (Box 3)
  - Pierce, Franklin, pres. U.S. (1804-1869).
    - ALS to Hannibal Hamlin. [n.p.], March 29 [1848]
      See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.58
    - ALS to William L. Marcy. [n.p.], [undated]
  - Pierce, John (1773-1849). ALS to Abijah R. Baker. Brookline, Mass., October 6, 1840 (Box 7)
  - Pierpont, John (1785-1866). ALS to Benjamin Silliman (1779-1864). Saratoga Springs, N.Y., July 25, 1826
    Transferred to Silliman Papers (MS 450).
  - Pinckney, Charles Cotesworth (1746-1825). ALS to Petit de Villers. Pinckney Island, S.C., October 31, 1815
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.12
  - Pischon, Carl Nath[aniel?]. ALS in German to Edwards A. Park. Athens, Greece, July 18, 1851 (Box 7)
  - Plumer, William Swan (1802-1880). ALS to an unnamed person. Pottsville, Pa., May 9, 1866 (Box 7)
  - Polk, James Knox, pres. U.S. (1795-1849). ALS to William L. Marcy. Washington, June 1, 1845
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.52
  - Porter, Ebenezer (1772-1834).
    - 2 ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. New Haven and Washington, Conn., October 18, 1811; December 20, 1811 (Box 3)
    - 2 ALS to Benjamin B. Wisner. Andover, Mass., March 14, 1831; May 19, 1831 (Box 6)
  - Power, Tyrone (1797-1841). ALS to J. R. Boyd. New York, October 19, 1838
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.57
  - Pratt, Josiah (1768-1844). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. London, August 30, 1833
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.36
  - Prescott, William Hickling (1796-1859). ALS to an unnamed person. Boston, May 28 [no year]
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.33
  - Price, Richard. ALS to an unnamed person. Hackney, March 22, 1788
  - Prince, Thomas (1687-1758). 2 ALS to the Rev. Mr. William McCullock. Boston:
    - May 7, 1742 (Box 1)
    - June 15, 1743
  - Pusey, Edward Bouverie (1800-1882). ALS to Leonard Woods (1807-1878). Oxford, England, [1840] (Box 7)
  - Quincy, Josiah (1772-1864).
    - 2 ALS to Samuel Farrar. Boston, August 25, 1813; October 29, 1813 (Box 4)
    - ALS to Edwards A. Park. Cambridge, Mass., September 13, 1844 (Box 7)
  - Raffles, Thomas (1788-1863). ALS to an unnamed person. Liverpool, February 14, 1859
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.35
  - Raguse, Auguste Frédéric Louis Viesse de Marmont, duke of (1774-1852). ALS in French to ________. [no place], April 4, 1836
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.57
  - Rammohun, Roy (1774-1833). ALS to Capt. A. Heard. [no place], January 1828
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.51
  - Randolph, John (1773-1833). AL (signed with initials) to Joseph A. Clay. Washington, January 13, 1820
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.20
  - Read, Thomas Buchanan (1822-1872), attributed author. Notes on several of his paintings noted by E. A. Park as probably written by Read, but not in his own hand. [no place, no date] (Box 8)
  - Reeve, Aaron Burr (1780-1809).
    - ALS to Tapping Reeve and Sarah (Burr) Reeve. New York, May 7, 1802 (Box 2)
    - ALS to Tapping Reeve. New York, December 9, 1808 (Box 3)
  - Reeve, Abner (1707/8-1798). ALS to Tapping and Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Brattleboro, Vt., August 29, 1778 (Box 1)
  - Reeve, Sarah (Burr) (1754-1797).
    - ALS to Timothy Edwards. Fairfield, Conn., March 9 [1770] (Box 1)
    - 2 ALS to Tapping Reeve. Fairfield, Conn.:
      - November 29, 1772 (Box 1)
      - [no place, undated] (Box 8)
  - Reeve, Tapping (1744-1823).
    - ALS to Timothy Edwards. Elizabethtown, N. J., May 24, 1769 (Box 1)
    - AL (not signed) to Mrs. Elizabeth Reeve. Danbury, Conn., July 20 [1801] (Box 2)
    - 7 ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Litchfield, Conn., November 29, 1769; [2 letters, no day, no month, 1772]; January 29, 1773; March 6, 1773; September 25, 1773; [no day, no month] 1773 (Box 1)
  - Reid, Mayne (1818-1883). ALS to Charles Tilt. Shelton church, Oxon., [undated] (Box 8)
  - Rice, Asaph. Letter of thanks to Nathaniel Emmons for his attack on Freemasonry, signed also by Ebenezer Blake and Samuel D. Green. Worcester, Mass., September 6, 1832 (Box 6)
  - Rice, John Holt (1777-1831). ALS to William Hill. Richmond, Va., February 15, 1817 (Box 4)
  - Richards, James (1767-1843). ALS to Anna S. (Richards) Beach. Auburn, N.Y., September 1, 1837 (Box 6)
  - Rippon, John (1751-1836). ALS to the Rev. Dr. Rogers. London, August 7, 1794
  - Ritter, Karl (1779-1859). Notes in German on geography; unsigned, undated
  - Robinson, Edward (1794-1863). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. New York, March 11, 1844
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.78
  - Robinson, Ezekiel Gilman (1815-1894). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Providence, R.I., September 26, 1876 (Box 7)
  - Rosenmueller, Ernst Friedrich Karl (1760-1835). 1 leaf of manuscript in German, [no place, no date]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.38
  - Rotteck, Karl Wenzeslaus Rodecker von (1775-1840). ALS in German to Klose. Freiburg, Germany, June 22, 1838
  - Rush, Richard (1780-1859). ALS to Asbury Dickins. Sydenham, near Philadelphia, January 19, 1840
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.40
  - Russell, Henry (1812-1900). ALS to General George Pope Morris. Boston, October 17, 1838
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.58
  - Russell, J. ALS to an unnamed person. Minto, September 1, 1857
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.37
  - Ryder, Henry (1777-1836). ALS to Thomas Heath. Stafford, July 15, 1829
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.38
  - Sage, Timothy. Receipt for goods received from Benedict Arnold. St. Croix [W.I.], January 21, 1774
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.20
  - St. Cyriaci, Stift, Braunschweig, Germany. Receipt in German for rentals and tithes to Canon J. G. Campe? Braunschweig, December 24, 1790
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.35
  - Schaff, Philip (1819-1893). ALS to Henry Darling. New York, October 17, 1877 (Box 7)
  - Schauffler, William Gottlieb (1798-1883). ALS to Ann Maria (Edwards) Park. New York, June 6, 1882 (Box 7)
  - Schleiermacher, Friedrich Ernst Daniel (1768-1834). Notes and a sermon, written in German, unsigned
  - Schuetz, Christian Gottfried (1747-1832?). 2 ALS in German to unnamed persons. Jena and Halle, Germany:
    - December 3?, 1800
    - November 27, 1824?
  - Schuyler, Philip John (1733-1804).
    - Copy of a letter to Timothy Edwards. Saratoga [N.Y.], April 1, 1778
    - ALS to Col. Yates, probably Robert. Saratoga [N.Y.], June 26, 1778
  - Scott, Sir Walter (1771-1832). ALS and facsimile to Charles Tilt. Melrose, Scot., [May 1, 1830]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.8
  - Scott, William Anderson (1813-1885). ALS to Abijah Eaker. New Orleans, May 30, 1853 (Box 7)
  - Scott, Winfield (1786-1866). ALS to A. Van Santvoord. Utica, October 31, 1813
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.26
  - Sears, Barnas (1802-1880). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Newton Centre, Mass., December 13, 1838 (Box 6)
  - Sedgwick, Catharine Maria (1789-1867). ALS to Mrs. Edwards. [no place, ca. 1836]
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.17
  - Sedgwick, Pamela (Dwight) (1754-1807). ALS to Aaron Burr. Sheffield, Mass., August 3, 1779 (Box 1)
  - Sedgwick, Theodore (1746-1813). ALS to Thomas Davis. Stockbridge [Mass.], September 19, 1792
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.19
  - Sergeant, John (1747-1824). Application for five hundred dollars of public money to be secured by a mortgage on his property. Oneida, N.Y., [1808]
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.10
  - Sewall, Elizabeth (Missing). ALS, apparently to an American publisher. Ventnor, Isle of Wight, March 22, 1849
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.50
  - Sewall, Joseph (1683-1769). Autograph list of persons married by Sewall in the year 1717. Boston
  - Seward, William Henry (1801-1872). ALS to Joshua A. Spencer. Auburn [N.Y.], June 16, 1839
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.52
  - Shedd, William Greenough Thayer (1820-1894). ALS to Edwards A. Park. New York, January 30, 1882 (Box 7)
  - Sigourney, Lydia Howard (Huntley) (1791-1865).
    - ALS to Ann Maria (Edwards) Park. Hartford, April 5, 1853
    - "Greenwood Cemetery," poem, not signed but in her hand. [no place], May 30, 1848
  - Silliman, Benjamin (1779-1864). ALS to Amos Eaton. New Haven, December 2, 1834
    Transferred to Silliman Papers.
  - Simms, William Gilmore (1806-1870). ALS to Rufus Wilmot Griswold. Charleston, S.C., June 7 [1842]
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.39
  - Simon, David Worthington (1830-1909). ALS to German to Edwards A. Park. Frankfort, Germany, [ca. July 1864] (Box 7)
  - Sinclair, Sir John, 1st bart. (1754-1835). ALS to an unnamed person. Ham Common, Surrey, August 28, 1818
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.24
  - Sinoh, Dulup. ALS to an unnamed person. Ballen________? Perthshire, Scot., August 10, 1870 (Box 7)
  - Skinner, Thomas Harvey (1791-1871).
    - ALS to Benjamin Blydenburg Wisner. Philadelphia, November 10, 1832 (Box 6)
    - ALS to an unnamed person. New York, December 10, 1864 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Alexander (1830-1867).
    - ALS to Mr. Dave Bogue. Edinburgh, October 24, 1856 (Box 7)
    - ALS to an unnamed person. Paisley, Scot., May 28 [1853?] (Box 7)
  - Smith, Goldwin (1823-1910). ALS to Edward Bach. Philadelphia, November 29, 1864
  - Smith, John Cotton (1765-1845). ALS to Tapping Reeve. Washington, March 8, 1802 (Box 2)
  - Smith, John Pye (1774-1851). ALS in French to Frédéric Joöl Jean Gérard Monod. Homerton College, Eng., April 10, 1850
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.52